Finding Aid for the Paul Jordan Smith Papers LSC.0267
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Books Inscribed to Paul Jordan Smith
  - Manuscripts. (Box 51)
    - -The Road I Came. (Box 51)
    - -Surprise Anthology. (Box 51)
  - Correspondence. (Box 52)
  - Ephemera - re Paul Jordan Smith lectures. (Box 52)
  - Photographs. (Box 52)
  - Pamphlets, newspaper clippings, and other ephemera collected by Paul Jordan Smith. (Box 52)
  - Reviews, unsorted material. (Box 54)
  - Manuscript for Nomad. (Box 55)
  - Correspondence and contracts with publishers. (Box 55)